<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CookMate</string>

    <!-- Pasta -->
    <string name="pastaIngredients">Pasta
\nCream Cheese
\nParmesan Cheese
\nOlive Oil
\nGarlic (minced)
\nSalt (to taste)
\nPepper (to taste)</string>
    <string name="pastaDesc">1. Cook your pasta in a large pot of salted boiling water until al dente (around 8-10 minutes).
\n2. While the pasta is cooking, heat olive oil in a skillet over medium heat. Add garlic and sauté until fragrant (about 1-2 minutes).
\n3. Add cream cheese to the skillet, followed by some of the pasta cooking water, stirring until the cheese melts and forms a creamy sauce.
\n4. Stir in parmesan cheese and mix well. Season with salt and pepper to taste.
\n5. Drain the pasta and add it to the skillet. Toss the pasta in the sauce, adding more pasta water if needed to reach your desired consistency.
\n6. Serve hot with extra parmesan on top if desired.</string>

    <!-- Maggi Noodles -->
    <string name="maggiIngredients">Maggi Noodles
\nWater (1.5 cups)
\nMaggi Masala (1 packet)</string>
    <string name="maggieDesc">1. In a pot, bring 1.5 cups of water to a boil.
\n2. Add the Maggi noodles and let it cook for about 2 minutes.
\n3. Stir in the Maggi Masala seasoning and mix well.
\n4. Continue to cook for another minute until the noodles are fully cooked and the flavors are well blended.
\n5. Serve hot, garnished with optional toppings like chopped vegetables or a boiled egg.</string>

    <!-- Cake -->
    <string name="cakeIngredients">All-purpose Flour
\nBaking Powder
\nEggs
\nSugar
\nButter (melted)
\nVanilla Extract
\nMilk
\nSalt</string>
    <string name="cakeDesc">1. Preheat your oven to 180°C (350°F). Grease and flour a round cake pan.
\n2. In a bowl, sift together flour, baking powder, and salt.
\n3. In a separate bowl, whisk eggs and sugar until light and fluffy.
\n4. Add melted butter and vanilla extract to the egg mixture and mix well.
\n5. Gradually add the dry ingredients to the wet ingredients, alternating with milk, and mix until smooth.
\n6. Pour the batter into the prepared cake pan and bake for 25-30 minutes or until a toothpick comes out clean.
\n7. Let the cake cool before serving. Optional: frost or decorate as desired.</string>

    <!-- Pancake -->
    <string name="pancakeIngredients">All-purpose Flour
\nBaking Powder
\nSugar
\nSalt
\nEggs
\nMilk
\nButter (melted)
\nVanilla Extract</string>
    <string name="pancakeDesc">1. In a large bowl, whisk together flour, baking powder, sugar, and salt.
\n2. In a separate bowl, beat the eggs, milk, melted butter, and vanilla extract together.
\n3. Pour the wet ingredients into the dry ingredients and stir until just combined. The batter should be lumpy, not smooth.
\n4. Heat a non-stick skillet or griddle over medium heat and lightly grease it with butter or oil.
\n5. Pour about 1/4 cup of batter onto the skillet for each pancake. Cook until bubbles form on the surface, then flip and cook for another 1-2 minutes.
\n6. Serve with maple syrup, fresh fruit, or your favorite toppings.</string>

    <!-- Pizza -->
    <string name="pizzaIngredients">Pizza Dough (store-bought or homemade)
\nTomato Sauce
\nMozzarella Cheese (shredded)
\nPepperoni or other toppings (optional)
\nOlive Oil
\nOregano</string>
    <string name="pizzaDesc">1. Preheat your oven to 220°C (425°F).
\n2. Roll out the pizza dough on a floured surface to your desired thickness.
\n3. Spread a thin layer of tomato sauce over the dough, leaving a border around the edges.
\n4. Sprinkle mozzarella cheese generously over the sauce.
\n5. Add your favorite toppings (e.g., pepperoni, vegetables).
\n6. Drizzle a little olive oil over the top and sprinkle with oregano.
\n7. Bake in the preheated oven for 10-12 minutes or until the crust is golden and the cheese is bubbly.
\n8. Slice and serve immediately.</string>

    <!-- Burgers -->
    <string name="burgerIngredients">Ground Beef Patties
\nBurger Buns
\nLettuce
\nTomato Slices
\nCheese (optional)
\nKetchup
\nMustard
\nPickles</string>
    <string name="burgerDesc">1. Preheat your grill or skillet over medium-high heat.
\n2. Season the ground beef patties with salt and pepper on both sides.
\n3. Grill or cook the patties for 3-4 minutes on each side, or until they reach your desired level of doneness.
\n4. Toast the burger buns on the grill for 1-2 minutes.
\n5. Assemble the burgers by placing a patty on the bottom bun, followed by cheese, lettuce, tomato, pickles, and your favorite condiments.
\n6. Place the top bun on and serve immediately with fries or a side salad.</string>

    <!-- Fries -->
    <string name="friesIngredients">Potatoes (cut into thin strips)
\nOlive Oil
\nSalt
\nPepper
\nGarlic Powder (optional)
\nPaprika (optional)</string>
    <string name="friesDesc">1. Preheat your oven to 200°C (400°F). Line a baking sheet with parchment paper.
\n2. Toss the potato strips in olive oil, salt, pepper, and any additional seasonings (garlic powder, paprika).
\n3. Spread the fries in a single layer on the baking sheet and bake for 25-30 minutes, flipping halfway through, until golden and crispy.
\n4. Serve hot with ketchup, mayo, or your favorite dipping sauce.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_detailed">Recipe Detail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_favorite_recipes">Favorite Recipe</string>
</resources>
